Step 1: click (453, 306) [OK]\NI can see a GitHub repository page for 'pphouse/screenpilot'. At the top of the page, there is a navigation bar with sev
Step 2: click (453, 306) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the GitHub repository page for 'pphouse/screenpilot'. At the top navigation bar, th
Step 3: find_and_click (505, 321) [OK]\NI can see the GitHub repository page for 'pphouse/screenpilot'. Looking at the navigation tabs near the top of the page,
Step 4: click (453, 306) [OK]\NI can see the GitHub repository page for 'pphouse/screenpilot'. Looking at the navigation tabs at the top, I can see: Co
Step 5: click (453, 306) [OK]\NI can see the GitHub repository page for 'pphouse/screenpilot'. Looking at the navigation tabs at the top, I can see: Co
Step 6: click (453, 306) [OK]\NI can see the GitHub repository page for 'pphouse/screenpilot'. Looking at the navigation tabs at the top, I can see: Co
Step 7: find_and_click (498, 321) [OK]\NI can see the GitHub repository page for 'pphouse/screenpilot'. Looking at the navigation tabs at the top, I can see: Co
Step 8: click (453, 306) [OK]\NI can see the GitHub repository page for 'pphouse/screenpilot'. Looking at the navigation bar, I can see several tabs: C
Step 9: click (453, 306) [OK]\NI can see the GitHub repository page for 'pphouse/screenpilot'. Looking at the navigation bar, I can see tabs including
Step 10: click (453, 306) [OK]\NI can see the GitHub repository page for 'pphouse/screenpilot'. Looking at the navigation bar, I can see tabs including